JEFERSON CARVALHO **FERREIRA**

+353 83 204 3170

Q jfz1r0@gmail.com

BUSINESS & I.T. CONSULTANT

ABOUT ME

I am an Business and I.T. consultant with six years experience in a wide variety of I.T. & business requirements. Configuration of networks & assembly and replacement of hardware. I have a passion for I.T. and problem solving, I am also in my spare time learning to code and become a Developer.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Business, Administrative Assistance, I.T. Operations & helpdesk

Universidade Ferderal do Cariri - Juazeiro do Norte, CE, Brazil

2014 - 2019

EXPERTISE

I.T. Repair & Business I.T. I.T. Sales, assembly & maintenance I.T. & Business support 6 vears Proactive & Team player Organized & critical thinker

EXPERIENCE

I.T. Salesman & Repair Webstore - Crato

Buying and selling new and used computers and parts, assembly and maintenance of gaming computers, replacement of parts and products according to demand.

Coach of MMA

Fight Sport - Crato, CE Viera Martial Arts - Dublin 1

Experienced in MMA, Muay Thai, Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu, Submission, Boxing and kick boxing.

Extensive experience with teaching children from 6 years old to young people and adults.

Intern Bank of Brazil

Banco do Brasil - Crato, CE

Issuing, distributing and collecting bank slips.

Organizing credit cards, cheques and customer accounts

Organizing & Maintaining payment Receipts from customers Banks Correspondence

January 2017 to 2022

June 2015 to Present

May 2013 - May 2015

CERTIFICATION

ILHA PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION 2020 to 2020

- Introduction to programming logic
- Advanced python
- Introduction to WEB development
- WEB Applications
- Advanced django

POSITIVO PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION 2009 to 2010

- laptop and desktop assembly and maintenance
- laboratory of technology
- Installation and Network configuration
- Installation of printers assembly
- Maintenance of training certification

FOX PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION 2008 to 2009

- laptop and desktop assembly and maintenance
- laboratory of technology
- Installation and Network configuration
- Installation printers assembly
- Maintenance training certification

FOX BASIC WEB DESIGNING AND **EDITOR CERTIFICATION** 2009 to 20010

- Basic Web design training HTMl
- · Video and Photo editing
- · Basic training in Adobe Premiere, Photoshop, illustrator, HTML and Corel

EXPERIENCE

LANGUAGES

ITechnical Support Agent Positivo- Juaziero do norte CE

Computer maintenance team manager in the Cariri region. Installation, maintenance and assembly of computer labs including network, printers, operating systems and computers for people with special needs..

Technical Support Agent Fox Informática - Crato, CE

Assembly and maintenance of computers, installation of operating system and software. Printer support and maintenance, network installation and support.

April 2011-May 2013

- English Intermediate
- Portuguese Native

January 2009-March 2011